A Guide to the Virginia District Pilot International records, 1947-2003
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia District Pilot International records, 1947-2003
The Library of Virginia
36420
10.2 cu. ft. and 23 boxes
Virginia District Pilot International
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Bobbie B. Hudson of Danville, Virginia, and Carolyn Cattle of Marion, Virginia.
Custodial History
Accessions 38675 and 43133 are interfiled with Accession 36420.
Historical Information
Pilot Internation was chartered as a service organization in Macon, Georgia, in 1921. The Virginia District began in 1937, when the first Pilot club in Virginia was established in Bristol. Currently, the Virginia District consists of thirteen clubs.
Scope and Content
Records, 1947-2003, of Virginia District Pilot International consisting of correspondence, directories, financial records, handbooks, histories, manuals, minutes, newsletters, notes, reports, rosters, surveys, and other papers which document and detail the history, organization, and goals of the Virginia District Pilot International.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Administrative Records, 1972-2000.
Series II: Meeting Minutes, 1974-1995.
Series III: Conventions and Fall Councils, 1973-1997.
Series IV: Governor's Bulletins, 1988-1996.
Series V: Handicapped/Disabled Professional Woman/Person of the Year, 1978-1995.
Series VI: Local Clubs, 1947, 1968-2003.
Series VII: Pilot International Papers, 1989-1998.
Series VIII: General Files and Ephemera.
Contents List
- Series I: Administrative Records, 1972-2000., Extent: 5 boxes. (Box 1-5)
  Administrative Records, 1972-2000, contain articles of incorporation, budgets, correspondence, financial papers, goals, handbooks, manuals, minutes, nominations, notes, reports, rosters, standing rules, surveys, and other papers concerning the administrative operations of the Virginia District Internation Pilot organization and its youth branch of Anchor Clubs.
  - Subseries 1: Articles of Incorporation, guidelines, and handbooks., 1 box (Box 1)
    - Articles of incorporation, 1979. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Standing rules. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Handbook (folder 1 of 2). (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Handbook (folder 2 of 2). (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Handbook. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Governor--District 11 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Governor--District 11 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - District Goals, 1996-1997. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Service with a Smile handbook, 1991-1992. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 2: Governor's Papers, 1991-1995., 1 box (Box 1)
    - Correspondence--governor and governor-elect, 1991-1992. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence--governor and governor-elect, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence--governor and governor-elect, 1994. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence--governor and governor-elect, 1995. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence--governor and governor-elect, no date. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 3: District Secretary's Minutes and Notes, 1994-2000., 1 box (Box 2)
    - District Secretary--minutes and notes, 1994-1995. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - District Secretary--minutes and notes, 1996-1997 (folder 1 of 3). (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - District Secretary--minutes and notes, 1996-1997 (folder 2 of 3). (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - District Secretary--minutes and notes, 1996-1997 (folder 3 of 3). (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - District Secretary--minutes and notes, 1997-1998 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - District Secretary--minutes and notes, 1997-1998 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - District Secretary--minutes and notes, 1999-2000 (folder 1 of 3). (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - District Secretary--minutes and notes, 1999-2000 (folder 2 of 3). (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - District Secretary--minutes and notes, 1999-2000 (folder 3 of 3). (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 4: Financial Records, 1978-1996., 1 box (Box 3)
    - Treasurer's reports and financial papers, 1983, 1988-1993. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Treasurer's reports and financial papers, 1994-1996. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Special committee--district budget. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Audits--reports and papers, 1978-1995. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Financial committee survey, 1995-1996 (folder 1 of 3). (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Financial committee survey, 1995-1996 (folder 2 of 3). (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Financial committee survey, 1995-1996 (folder 3 of 3). (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 5: Officers and Coordinators, 1977-1996., 2 boxes (Box 3-4)
    - District appointments and officers. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - District coordinators--communications and information, 1989-1991, 1994-1996. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Nominations, 1977-1979. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Nominations, 1979-1980. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Nominations, 1980-1981. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Nominations, 1981-1982. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Nominations, 1982-1983. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Nominations, 1983-1984. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Nominations, 1984-1985. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Nominations, 1985-1986. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Nominations, 1986-1987. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Nominations, 1987-1988. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Nominations, 1988-1989. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Nominations, 1989-1990. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Nominations, 1990-1991. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Nominations, 1991-1992. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Nominations, 1992-1993. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Nominations, 1993-1994. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Nominations, 1994-1995, 1995-1996. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Officers training, 1992-1993. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - District leadership training (folder 1 of 2). (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - District leadership training (folder 2 of 2). (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 6: Membership and Growth, 1988-1996., 2 boxes (Box 4-5)
    - Virginia District roster, 1991-1992. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Virginia District roster, 1994-1995. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Membership roster drafts, 1994-1995 (folder 1 of 3). (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Membership roster drafts, 1994-1995 (folder 2 of 3). (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Membership roster drafts, 1994-1995 (folder 3 of 3). (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Membership reports, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Membership reports, 1994. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Membership reports, 1995-1996, no date. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - District membership. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Members-at-large, 1992-1993. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Extensions, 1988-1991. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Pilot growth guidelines. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Pilot growth training manuals, 1988. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Pilot growth team manual, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Growth team, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Growth team, 1993-1996, no date. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 7: Anchor Clubs, 1972-1996., 1 box (Box 5)
    - Anchor Club handbooks and manuals. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Anchor Clubs, 1972, 1985, 1991-1992. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Anchor Clubs, 1993-1996, no date. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 8: Reports, Programs, etc., 1991-1995., 1 box (Box 5)
    - Projects division. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Fundraising division. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Seniors programs, 1991-1992, 1994-1995. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Founders Day, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Series II: Meeting Minutes, 1974-1995., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 5-6)
  Meeting Minutes, 1974-1995, contains minutes and other papers recording the meetings of the District Administrative Council (DAC) and the Board of Directors of the Virginia District Pilot International.
  - Subseries 1: District Administrative Council (DAC) minutes, 1974-1995., 2 boxes (Box 5-6)
    - District Administrative Council (DAC) minutes, 1974. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - DAC minutes, 1975. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - DAC minutes, 1976. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - DAC minutes, 1978. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - DAC minutes, 1979. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - DAC minutes, 1980. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - DAC minutes, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - DAC minutes, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - DAC minutes, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - DAC minutes, 1984. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - DAC minutes, 1985. (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - DAC minutes, 1986. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - DAC minutes, 1987. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - DAC minutes, 1988. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - DAC minutes, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - DAC minutes, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - DAC minutes, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - DAC minutes, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - DAC minutes, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - DAC minutes, 1994. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - DAC minutes, 1995. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 2: Board of Directors Minutes, 1979-1993., 1 box (Box 6)
    - Board of Directors minutes,. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Series III: Conventions and Fall Councils, 1973-1997., Extent: 6 boxes. (Box 6-11)
  Conventions and Fall Councils, 1973-1997, contain agendas, budgets, correspondence, fliers, minutes, notes, programs, reports, speeches, surveys, and other papers detailing district conventions and fall councils, as well as some Pilot International national conventions.
  - Fall Council, 1973. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Annual Convention, 1974. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Fall Council, 1974. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Annual Convention, 1975. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Fall Council, 1975. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Annual Convention, 1976. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Annual Convention, 1979. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Fall Council, 1979. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Annual Convention, 1980. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Fall Council, 1980. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Annual Convention, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Fall Council, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Annual Convention, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Fall Council, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Annual Convention, 1983. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Fall Council, 1983. (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Annual Convention, 1984. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Fall Council, 1984. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Annual Convention, 1985. (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Fall Council, 1985. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Annual Convention, 1986. (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Fall Council, 1987. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Fall Council, 1988. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Annual Convention, 1989 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Annual Convention, 1989 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Fall Council, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Annual Convention, 1990 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Annual Convention, 1990 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Annual Convention, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Fall Council, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Annual Convention, 1992 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Annual Convention, 1992 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Fall Council, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Annual Convention, 1993 (folder 1 of 7). (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Annual Convention, 1993 (folder 2 of 7). (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Annual Convention, 1993 (folder 3 of 7). (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Annual Convention, 1993 (folder 4 of 7). (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Annual Convention, 1993 (folder 5 of 7). (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Annual Convention, 1993 (folder 6 of 7). (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Annual Convention, 1993 (folder 7 of 7). (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - National Annual Convention, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Fall Council, 1993 (folder 1 of 5). (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Fall Council, 1993 (folder 2 of 5). (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Fall Council, 1993 (folder 3 of 5). (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Fall Council, 1993 (folder 4 of 5). (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Fall Council, 1993 (folder 5 of 5). (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Annual Convention, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - National Annual Convention, 1994 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - National Annual Convention, 1994 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Fall Council, 1994 (folder 1 of 4). (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Fall Council, 1994 (folder 2 of 4). (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Fall Council, 1994 (folder 3 of 4). (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fall Council, 1994 (folder 4 of 4). (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Annual Convention, 1995 (folder 1 of 4). (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Annual Convention, 1995 (folder 2 of 4). (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Annual Convention, 1995 (folder 3 of 4). (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Annual Convention, 1995 (folder 4 of 4). (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - National Annual Convention, 1995. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Fall Council, 1995 (folder 1 of 4). (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Fall Council, 1995 (folder 2 of 4). (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Fall Council, 1995 (folder 3 of 4). (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Fall Council, 1995 (folder 4 of 4). (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Annual Convention, 1996 (folder 1 of 7). (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Annual Convention, 1996 (folder 2 of 7). (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Annual Convention, 1996 (folder 3 of 7). (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Annual Convention, 1996 (folder 4 of 7). (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Annual Convention, 1996 (folder 5 of 7). (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Annual Convention, 1996 (folder 6 of 7). (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Annual Convention, 1996 (folder 7 of 7). (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Annual Convention, 1997. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - District convention planning. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Pilot District convention handbook, 1989. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Pilot District convention handbook, 1989. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - District convention handbook. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Annual convention suggested agenda. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Annual Convention/Fall Council parliamentary procedure. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Annual Convention/Fall Council miscellaneous papers. (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Series IV: Governor's Bulletins, 1988-1996., Extent: 1 box. (Box 11)
  Governor's Bulletins, 1988-1996, consist of the Governor's Bulletin newsletter containing news of the district, the district clubs, and the national organization, as well as related papers.
  - Governor's Bulletins, 1988-1989. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Bulletins, 1989-1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Bulletins, 1991-1992. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Bulletins, 1992-1993. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Bulletins, 1995-1996. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Bulletins related papers. (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Series V: Handicapped/Disabled Professional Woman/Person of the Year, 1978-1995., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 11-12)
  Handicapped/Disabled Professional Woman/Person of the Year, 1978-1995, contains biographies, correspondence, nomination forms, photographs, and other papers regarding the Virginia District award to disabled individuals. Candidates were nominated by individual clubs.
  - Handicapped Professional Woman of the Year, 1978. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Handicapped Professional Woman of the Year, 1979. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Handicapped Professional Woman of the Year, 1980. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Handicapped Professional Woman of the Year, 1981. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Handicapped Professional Woman of the Year, 1982. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Handicapped Professional Woman of the Year, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Handicapped Professional Woman of the Year, 1984. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Handicapped Professional Woman of the Year, 1985. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Handicapped Professional Woman of the Year, 1986. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Handicapped Professional Woman of the Year, 1987. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Handicapped Professional Woman of the Year, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Disabled Professional Woman of the Year, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Disabled Professional Woman of the Year, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Disabled Professional Woman of the Year, 1991. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Disabled Professional Woman of the Year, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Disabled Professional Person of the Year, 1993. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Disabled Professional Person of the Year, 1994. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Disabled Professional Person of the Year, 1995. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Disabled Professional Person of the Year related papers. (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Series VI: Local Clubs, 1947, 1968-2003., Extent: 9 boxes. (Box 12-20)
  Local Clubs, 1947, 1968-2003, contain agendas, awards, badges, clippings, correspondence, financial records, forms, handbooks, histories, minutes, newsletters, photographs, plaques, reports, rosters, speeches, yearbooks, and related papers concerning the organization and activities of the local clubs in the Virginia District Pilot International and their relation to the Virginia District.
  - Albemarle/Charlottesville, 1982, 1984, 1992-1994. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Albemarle/Charlottesville, 1995-1996, no date. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Bristol, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Bristol, 1991-1994. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Bristol, 1995-1997. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Bristol: handbooks, 1991-1994. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Bristol: handbooks, 1994-1997. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Chesapeake, 1972-1987, 1993-1996. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Luncheon Chesapeake, 1977-1985. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Luncheon Chesapeake, 1990-1996. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Danville, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Danville, 1990-1991. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Danville, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Danville, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Danville, 1994. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Danville, 1995-1996, no date. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Luncheon Danville, 1974-1984. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Luncheon Danville, 1990-1991. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Luncheon Danville, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Luncheon Danville, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Luncheon Danville, 1994. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Luncheon Danville, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Luncheon Danville, 1996-1997, no date. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Luncheon Danville: handbooks, 1992-1993, no date. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Luncheon Danville: handbooks, 1993-1995. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Luncheon Danville: Handbook, 1995-1996. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Luncheon Danville: handbooks, 1996-1997 (2 copies). (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Franklin/Southampton, 1990-1991. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Franklin/Southampton, 1992-1993. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Franklin/Southampton, 1994-1996, no date. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hampton Roads, 1972-1984, 1995-1996. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Harrisonburg, 1970-1985. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Harrisonburg, 1990-1992. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Harrisonburg, 1993-1995. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Harrisonburg, 1996. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Harrisonburg, 1997, no date. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Harrisonburg: yearbook, 1991-1992. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Harrisonburg: yearbook, 1994-1995[?]. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Harrisonburg: yearbook, 1996-1997[?]. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Isle of Wight, 1995-1997. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Marion: club charter, 28 February 1947. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Marion: minutes (business), May 1980-April 1983. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Marion: minutes (executive), May 1980-May 1984. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Marion: minutes, June 1983-May 1991 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Marion: minutes, June 1983-May 1991 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Marion: minutes and treasurer's reports, June 1991-September 1995 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Marion: minutes and treasurer's reports, June 1991-September 1995 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Marion: minutes, etc., 1995-1998 (folder 1 of 3). (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Marion: minutes, etc., 1995-1998 (folder 2 of 3). (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Marion: minutes, etc., 1995-1998 (folder 3 of 3). (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Marion: minutes, etc., 1998-2001. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Marion: minutes, 1999-2003. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Marion: treasurer's reports, 2001. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Marion: treasurer's reports, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Marion: treasurer's reports, 2003. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Marion: accounts payable, 2002-2003. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Marion: checkbook. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Marion: bank statements. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Marion, 1972-1982, 1985. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Marion, 1991. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Marion, 1992. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Marion, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Marion, 1994-1995. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Marion, 1996. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Marion, 1997. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Marion, 1998-2003. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Marion: Pilot International, 2001-2003. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Marion: Virginia District Pilot International, 2002-2003. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Marion: yearbooks, 1968-1983, 1986-1987. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Marion: yearbooks, 1987-1991. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Marion: yearbooks, 1992-1995. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Marion: yearbooks, 1995-2000, 2002-2003. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Marion: history. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Marion: clippings. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Marion: photographs. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Marion: badges, patches, and pins. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Marion: awards and certificates. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Marion: articles of termination, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Norfolk, 1972-1984, 1995-1996. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Outer Banks, 1984, 1991-1995. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Outer Banks, 1996-1997. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Outer Banks: yearbooks, 1994-1996. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Outer Banks: yearbook, 1996 (2 copies). (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Portsmouth, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Portsmouth, 1990-1996. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Richmond, 1970-1988. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Richmond, 1990-1992. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Roanoke, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Roanoke, 1991-1992. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Roanoke, 1993-1994. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Roanoke, 1995-1997. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Roanoke: yearbooks, 1991-1996. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Suffolk, 1975-1985. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Suffolk, 1993-1997. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Suffolk: yearbook and roster, 1996-1997[?], no date. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Beach, 1978-1985, 1991-1995. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Williamsburg, 1977-1984, 1991-1994. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Williamsburg: yearbook, 1992-1994. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Winchester, 1972-1984. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Winchester, 1990-1991. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Winchester, 1992. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Winchester, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Winchester, 1994-1995. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Winchester, 1996-1997, no date. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Official visits, 1986-1987. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Official visits, 1989-1991. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Official visits, 1992-1993. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Official visits, 1994-1995. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Official visit forms. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Official speeches, addresses, and comments. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Official visits: miscellaneous papers. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Awards, 1989-1995. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Pilot Excellence Program (PEP), 1989-1995. (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Series VII: Pilot International Paper, 1989-1998., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 20-21)
  Pilot International Papers, 1989-1998, consist of articles of incorporation, by-laws, correspondence, directories, financial records, manuals, magazines, minutes, programs, reports, and other papers concerning the national organization and its foundation, the Pilot International Foundation, as well as Pilot International's relation with the Virginia District.
  - Subseries 1: Administrative Papers,., 1 box (Box 20)
    - Articles of incorporation. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - By-laws and amendments (including the Pilot International Foundation). (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1992. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1995. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Reports. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Annual report, 1995. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Finances and budgets. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Training for district governors, 1992. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - leadership workshop. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 2: Papers and Correspondence, 1989-1998., 2 boxes (Box 20-21)
    - Papers, 1989-1992. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Papers, 1993-1994. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - 1995,. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - 1996,. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Member-at-large letters (Virginia District), 1995-1998. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Papers, no date. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 3: Pilot International Foundation, 1992-1996., 1 box (Box 21)
    - Papers, 1992-1993. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Papers, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 4)